# Mike Vanbuskirk

DevOps Engineer | Grand Rapids, MI | linkedin.com/in/mikevanbuskirk

### summary

Lead engineer specializing in DevOps, cloud-first architecture, and automation.

I'm passionate about technology, like solving difficult problems, and never pass up an opportunity to expand my skillset. Experience building solutions in some of the largest CDN, Cloud, and E-Commerce platforms in the world.

Before I joined the tech industry, my background was in customer service, sales, and marketing.

### experience

Nov 2022 - Present | Truffle Security Senior DevOps Engineer Design and implement cloud software deployments and infrastructure using IaC, CI/CD, and AI. Mar 2022 - Oct 2022 | CoinList Senior DevOps Engineer Designing and implementing automated, end-to-end cloud software deployments for data and application teams using IaC and CI/CD. May 2021 - Mar 2022 | Altitude Networks Lead Infrastructure Engineer Managed and modernized large serverless infrastructure deployment with Terraform. May 2020 - Present | **IOD** Freelance Technical Writer Provide expert technical content with a marketing focus to a variety of technology industry names. Feb 2019 - May 2021 | Salesforce Lead DevOps Engineer Supported two large-scale, customer facing SaaS products. Built cost analytics ETL platform using serverless. Dec 2017 - Feb 2019 | Apptio Senior DevOps Engineer Supported multiple service teams in building cloud applications. Designed and deployed multi-account IAM SSO infrastructure. Jul 2016 - Nov 2017 | The Walt Disney Company Senior Systems Engineer Built greenfield infrastructure deployments and provided operational support to Tier-1 services used by multiple Disney properties. Aug 2014 - Jul 2016 | Amazon Technical Operations Support Engineer Provided operational support and contributed to service infrastructure buildout to AWS and Amazon.com

#### education

2009 - 2012 WGU | BSc - Networks Design & Management

Jun 2013 - Aug 2014 | Centurylink/Level(3) CDN NOC Linux Admin

Linux sysadministration and NOC operational support for a major, nationally distributed CDN.

## languages & technology

I'm most comfortable in Python, but can be productive in Bash, Golang, and a bit of Javascript. I've worked with a broad variety of tools, platforms, and philosophies within the SDLC.